あのタワーがある限り　私は自由になれない
I'll never be free, as long as that tower still stands.
少年少女輪になって
shounen shoujo wa ni natte
The boys and girls form a ring
伸ばした手は空を切って落ちる
nobashita te wa kuu wo kitte ochiru
Extended hands cut down through the air
交わらないイマジナリー
majiwaranai imaginary
The Imaginary and the Real can never mingle
回転木馬宙を舞って
kaiten mokuba chuu wo matte
The merry-go-round twirls into the air
戦いの幕を切って落とす
tatakai no maku wo kitte otosu
As the curtain of war is torn open
秘め事明かすホーリーナイト
himegoto akasu holy night
The Holy Night for divulging secrets
真夜中開く窓
mayonaka hiraku mado temaneku nazo no koe
My window opens at night and a mysterious voice beckons
手招く謎の声
深紅のカーテンを翻して
shinku no curtain wo hirugaeshite hohoemi kakusu
A crimson curtain conceals the smile
微笑み隠す
少年よ我に帰れ
shounen yo ware ni kaere
Boys, come back to me
特急列車乗っちゃって
tokkyuu ressha nocchate
I ended up getting on the midnight express
ネパーランドに連れてって
neverland ni tsuretette
Take me away to Neverland
一切合切奪ってよ
issai gassai ubatte yo
Steal away everything I have
後ろ指さされたって
ushiro yubi sasaretatte
I don't care if you talk behind my back
一目散に逃げちゃっていいよ
ichimokusan ni nigechatte iiyo
I'll just run away at full speed
全部お気に召すまま
zenbu oki ni mesu mama
Do as you please
少年少女輪になって
shounen shoujo wa ni natte
The boys and girls form a ring
伸ばした手は空を切って落ちる
nobashita te wa kuu wo kitte ochiru
Extended hands cut down through the air
回り始めるディステニー
mawari hajimeru destiny
Destiny begins to turn
本字幕由诸神字幕组(www.kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
时间轴：wcaster  压制：wcaster
日听 xHunter 翻译：小音 校对：要命的小宇、木落
いやー　ついてたよ
I won the Suzuran Street raffle.
鈴蘭通りの福引きんゲット
Shaky tower on the verge of collapsing now
まさか温泉旅行が当たるとはなー
I never thought I'd score hot a spring resort package!
って　何だよ
What's the matter?
I let you come along! Why the long face?
せっかく連れてきてやったのに
暗いな
振られたくらいで　くよくよすんなよ
Don't be all depressed over being rejected by a girl!
次　俺の番だろ
Aw, man! It's my turn next!
もうー
Damn.
そういあ　先廊下ですっげぇ綺麗なお姉さん見つけたんだ
By the way, I saw this seriously hot chick in the hallway.
隣の部屋らしいぜ
And get this: she's right next door!
I'm sure she's a celebrity.
きっと芸能人だ　お忍び旅行ってやつかな
Must be traveling incognito!
今頃隣で彼氏としっぽり
She might be getting it on with her boyfriend just beyond that wall!
Shoma - Shinjuku Gyoen Station -- Near the Station - This Afternoon - I may have said a horrible thing to her. I'm sure she was hurt by my words.
Enough already!
やめてくれよ
言い過ぎたよな
I was probably too hard on her.
とりあえず　聞いとくか
I guess I'll listen to what she has to say.
晶馬君　あたしもうめちゃくちゃにされちゃうから
Shoma, I'm going to get all messed up.
全部貴方のせいだからね
It's all your fault!
以上でメッセージの再生は終了します
End of the message.
このメッセージをもう一度再生したい方
If you would like to hear the message agai-
What?
何だよ　もうー
What was that about?
もしもし　荻野目さん
Hello? Oginome?
何　もう手遅れよ
What do you want?
You're too late.
あたしは子供の貴方には到底理解出来ない世界に行くの
I'm off to a world that a child like you could never comprehend.
What does that mean?
何言ってるんだよ
Where are you going?
何処に行くって
これから貴方の知らない色んな事をされちゃうんだから
I'm about to experience things that you can't even imagine.
あんな所や　自分でも見たこともないそんな所とかを
I'm going to get turned inside out from interesting places...
裏返しにされたりするの
Places I've never even seen myself!
W-Wait!
待て　はやまるな
Think it through!
もっと自分を大切にしなきゃだめだ
You have to take better care of yourself!
ヤケ起こして後悔するような真似は
Don't do anything stupid that you'll regret later!
I'm going to break out of my cocoon and become a beautiful butterfly.
あたしは蛹を破って綺麗な蝶になるの
ジャーネ
Au revoir!
Wait!
バーカ　人生は長い
You have a long life ahead of you!
Bugs have a very short lifespan!
昆虫の一生は短いんだぞ
もしもし　もしもし
Hello? Hello?
バーカ
Dummy!
もしもーし　もしもし
Hello? Hello?
荻野目さん　しっかり
Oginome, get yourself together!
I'm heading your way now!
今すぐそっちに行くから
しまった　ここ東京じゃない
Oh, crap! I'm not in Tokyo!
Whoa, our neighbors are getting busy!
御隣さん　なんか盛り上がってきたみたいだぜ
Oginome, pick up the phone!
荻野目さん　電話に出て
Don't be afraid.
怖がらなくていいわ
Hello?
さあ　足を開いて
Now, spread your legs.
"Spread your legs!"
足を開けって
お姉さん　もしかして　女王様系
Is she a dominatrix?
硬くなってるわね
You're all stiff.
力を抜いて
Relax.
大丈夫　痛いのは最初だけ
Don't worry, it only hurts at first.
"All stiff?"
硬くなってる　力を抜いて
"Relax?"
痛いのは最初だけ
"It only hurts at first?"
Huh?
愛の桃源郷　快楽のエルドラドに連れていてあげるわ
I'll take you to Shangri-La of love, the El Dorado of pleasure.
"Shangri-La of love?!"
愛の桃源郷
"E-El Dorado of pleasure..."
快  快楽のエルドラド
隣か
They're next door?!
ちょっと待った
Hold it right there!
ゆ　百合さん
M-Ms. Yuri?
あら　紳士ならノックぐらいするものよ
Oh, my! A gentleman should at least knock.
Why are you...
貴方は
女が快楽を得るのも男が必要なんて
Who says women need men to find pleasure?
誰が決めたの
リンゴちゃんの大切な物は
Ringo's you-know-what is mine.
私が頂くわ
S-Stop!
やめろ
Oh, to be so young.
若いわね
The knight in shining armor saving the princess.
御姫様を救うナイト　可愛いじゃない
How cute.
私にもそんな情熱があれば　よかった
If only I had that kind of passion.
ありのままの私を見てと
If only I had the the desire to be wanted by others,
相手に求められる無邪気さがあれば
the naiveté to demand others to see me as who I am.
Yuri - The Room Where That Tower Can be Seen - The Ugly Duckling Play - I love Daddy. Because he's an artist. I'm willing to do anything for him.
あのタワーがある限り　私は自由になれない
I'll never be free, as long as that tower still stands.
私のパパは有名な芸術家
My daddy is a famous artist.
百合は美しい物が好きかい
Do you like beautiful things, Yuri?
ええ　パパ
Yes, Daddy.
じゃ　美しい物を作るパパは好きかい
Then, do you like your daddy, who makes beautiful things?
勿論　大好きよ
Of course I do!
私もだよ
I feel the same way.
いや　美しい物しか愛せない
Or rather, I can only love beautiful things.
芸術家だからね
After all, I am an artist.
百合　お前はなんて醜いんだろう
Yuri...
Why are you so... ugly?
醜い物は誰からも愛されない
The ugly are loved by no one.
ママを見ただろう
Just look at your mother.
ママは百合を産んでからどんどん醜くなってしまった
Your mother became uglier by the minute after she gave birth to you.
だから　もう　この家にはいられずあんな事になってしまったんだよ
That's why she could no longer live in this house and ended up like that.
ママ
Mommy...
ママは醜くそして愚かだった
Your mother was ugly and stupid too.
パパの芸術が理解出来なかったんだ
She couldn't comprehend Daddy's art.
いいかい　百合
Listen well, Yuri.
美しくない子供は誰にも愛されない
Ugly children are loved by no one.
They don't have the right to be loved.
その資格がないんだよ
百合　お前は醜い
Yuri, you are ugly.
No one will ever love you at this rate.
このままでは誰にも愛されない
Myself included, of course.
勿論　パパも百合を愛せない
私はそんなに醜いの
Am I that ugly?
ママの子だからね
You are your mother's child, after all.
でもパパなら　百合の体から余分な物を取り除いて
But Daddy can chip away the impurity from your body,
such that only beauty remains.
美しい子供にすることが出来る
彼のミケランジェロが大理石の中から見事なダビデ像を掘り出したようにね
Just as the great Michelangelo carved the
magnificent David from a block of marble.
ホ　ホント
R-Really?
ああ
Yes.
だからお願いがあるんだ
So, I have a favor to ask of you.
パパの手で百合を美しく改造させておくれ
Let Daddy remodel you into a true beauty.
パパにお前を愛させて欲しい
Let Daddy love you.
パパは美しい物しか愛せないのだから
After all, Daddy can only love beautiful things.
パパ
Daddy...
パパは百合を愛したいんだよ
Daddy wants to love you, Yuri.
パパ　私なんでもするよ
Daddy!
I'll do anything!
なんでもするから　私を愛して
Anything!
So please, love me!
いい子だ　百合
Good girl, Yuri.
いい子だ
That's a good girl.
パパも嬉しいよ
You make your daddy very happy.
パパのアトリエの窓からは
I can always see the tower from the window of Daddy's atelier.
いつもあのタワーが見える
では　お友達と二人一組になって
Pair up and draw each other's portraits.
お互いの顔描いてみましょう
Yes!
はーい
ね　一緒に描こう
Wanna draw with me?
Sure.
いいよ　　（先生　田中君が）
Teacher, Tanaka is...
やっぱりそうなんだ
He was right.
醜い物は誰からも選ばれない
The ugly are chosen by no one.
パパは正しい
Daddy was right.
So I have to continue...
だから私はもっともっと
時籠さん
Tokikago!
よかったら　時籠さんのこと描かせてくれない
Would you let me draw you?
どうして
Why me?
Because you're really beautiful!
だって　時籠さんとっても綺麗だから
What?
Wow! I've never won a golden award before!
凄い
金メダルなんて始めてだよ
やぱりモデルがよかったからかな
I guess I was blessed with a great model!
荻野目さん
Oginome.
桃果でいいよ
Call me Momoka.
ね　一緒に帰ろう
Come on, let's go home together.
私帰りにいつも餌あげてるんだ
I always feed them on the way home.
時籠さんもどう
Wanna try?
やらない
No.
どうして
How come? They're cute.
可愛いよ
嫌いなの
I hate them.
醜いアヒルの子ってお話知ってる
Have you ever heard of "The Ugly Duckling"?
うん
Yeah.
私あの話大嫌い
I hate that story.
Why?
どうして
だって　全部嘘だもの
Because it's all lies.
醜いアヒルの子が朝起きたら
How can an ugly duckling possibly become a beautiful swan overnight?
突然美しい白鳥になってるなんてあるわけない
Hmm... I guess.
まあーね
醜い物はね
Ugly things have to endure whatever pain it takes to become beautiful.
美しくなるために　どんな辛い事でも我慢しなきゃならないの
我慢して　我慢して
Endure until they becomes beautiful...
そして　美しくなった時
Only then, they can be loved.
やっと皆に愛してもらえるの
でも醜いアヒルの子って　ホントにいるのかな
But... are there really ugly ducklings?
Huh?
前に動物園で白鳥の赤ちゃん見たことあるけど
I saw a baby swan in the zoo before,
but I never thought it was ugly.
私はちっとも醜いなんて思わなかったよ
私は皆綺麗だと思うな
I think everything in this world is beautiful.
空も鳥も虫も蛙も花も石ころも
The sky, birds, bugs, frogs, flowers, and even rocks.
この世界は神様が創ったんだって
Because, if God created this world
だったら　汚くて醜い物なんてあるのかな
could there really be anything dirty and ugly in it?
あるわよ
There is.
だって　パパが
My daddy said...
時籠さんのパパ
Your daddy?
百合でいいよ
Call me Yuri.
さよなら
Bye!
今日は遅かったね
You're home late today.
寄り道でもしたのかい
Did you take a detour?
はい
Yes... a little.
少し
お友達でも出来たのかな
Did you make a friend?
Huh?
はい
Yes.
That's great. Is she nice?
それはよかった
素敵な子かな
はい
Yes.
では　その子を信じちゃだめだ
Then, you can't trust her.
えー
What?
Nice girls are nice to everyone.
素敵な子って言うのはね
誰にだっていい顔するんだ
自分が如何に素敵ないい子かって事をアピールするためにね
To appeal just how nice they are.
そういう子に限って
Those girls will say nice things to your face and then stab you in the back.
甘い事を言った後平気で裏切る
他人を信じちゃだめだ
Do not trust strangers.
信じていいのは血の繋がった家族だけなんだ
Only blood-related family members can to be trusted.
家族は嘘をつかない
Family members never lie.
Pure and beautiful love exist only among family.
純粋で美しい愛は家族にしかない
他人は全てママと同じ
Strangers are all like your mother.
百合にはパパしかいない
You have only me.
I have only you.
パパにも百合しかいない
つまり
In other words,
本当に百合を愛せるのはパパだけなんだよ
I'm the only person who can truly love you.
パパ
Daddy!
分かったら　早くこっちに来なさい
Hurry over here if you understand.
はい　パパ
Okay, Daddy.
Let's go to Tanaka's house after school!
ねね　宿題やった
Hey, did you do your homework?
百合　おはよう
Morning, Yuri!
もう私に構わないで
Don't talk to me again.
どうしたの
What's the matter?
また　怪我したの
Another wound?
私は貴方を信じない
I won't trust you.
こんな所に呼び出して　何の用
Why did you call me out here?
私の事信じてもらおうと思って
I want to get you to trust me.
ほっておいて
Leave me alone!
どうせ私が醜くて可哀相だから
You only talked to me out of pity because I'm so ugly and pathetic.
ちょっと構っただけでしょう
そんなことない
That's not true.
私百合の事大好きだよ
I love you a lot, Yuri.
嘘
That's a lie. You only love yourself for being nice.
好きなのは良い子の自分でしょう
じゃ　私の秘密教えたら信じてくれる
Would you believe me if I let you in on my secret?
秘密って　何
What secret?
私ね　運命の乗り換えが出来るの
I can transfer onto another fate...
この日記にある呪文を言って
by chanting a spell from this diary, and praying to God.
神様にお願いするの
そうするとね
Then I can transfer onto another fate, just like making a transfer on the subway.
電車を乗り換えるみたいに　運命を乗り換える事が出来るの
意味分かんない
You're not making any sense.
あのね　内緒だよ
This is our little secret, okay?
飼育小屋の兎　運命を乗り換えたんだよ
I transferred the rabbit at school onto another fate.
What?
あの兎ホントは死ぬはずだったの
That rabbit was actually supposed to die.
でも　私が呪文を使って　あの子の運命を変えたの
But I used the spell and changed her fate.
That's can't be true.
嘘よ
The rabbit at school was always healthy.
飼育小屋の兎は前から元気だったわ
The scenery of the world changes when a fate is changed.
一つの運命が変わると
世界の風景が変わってしまうの
だけど　皆は変わった事に気が付かない
But no one notices the change.
でも私だけは体ごと覚えている
But my body remembers.
何
What's that?
これは代償
It's the price.
運命を乗り換える呪文を使うと
You get punished when you use the spell to transfer fate.
罰を受けるんだ
乗り換えてみる
Would you like to try?
百合の運命
Would you like to transfer to another fate, Yuri?
乗り換えてみる
だって　このままだと
At this rate, you'll die.
百合は死んでしまう
だから　私が呪文を使って　百合を自由にしてあげる
So, I'll free you using my spell.
百合のためなら　もう一つ絆創膏が増えても
I wouldn't mind getting another bandage for you-
Don't be stupid!
バカ言わないで
私が自由になれるはずがない
How can I be free?
あのタワーはパパなの
That tower is my daddy.
いつも私を見ている
He's always watching me.
あれがこの世から消えない限り
As long as that tower still stands, I'll never...
タワーを消せばいいの
I just have to make that tower disappear?
そうよ
That's right.
出来るわけないでしょう
It's not possible, right?
I think it is.
出来ると思うよ
嘘
That's a lie.
No, it's not.
嘘じゃないよ
人をからかってそんなに面白い
Is messing with me really that fun?
私が醜いから
Is it because I'm ugly?
でもそれも今日で終り
But that will end today.
だって　パパが言ってたもの
My daddy told me:
今日で全てが終わるって
"Everything will end today."
明日になれば　私は
Tomorrow, I'll...
No!
だめ
You'll die before that!
その前に死んじゃうよ
お願いだから　やめて
Please, don't!
嫌よ
No! If I have to live without ever being loved,
醜いまま誰にも愛されずに生きるくらいなら
I'd rather die and become a swan!
死んで　白鳥になった方がまし
百合
Yuri!
Liar! I hate you!
嘘つき　大嫌い
百合　ようやくフィレンツェから新しい鑿が届いたよ
Yuri.
The new chisel from Firenze has finally arrived.
覚悟はいいね　百合
Are you ready?
今日は最後のお仕事
It's the pièce de résistance.
これでお前は永遠にパパに愛される存在になるんだ
You'll become something Daddy will love for all eternity.
最高の傑作になる
My ultimate masterpiece.
さあ　行くよ
Are you ready?
はい　パパ
Yes, Daddy.
To'oh General Hospital
Our next guest is Double-H.
さて　次のゲストはダブルエイチの二人
Hibari and Hikari.
雲雀ちゃんと光莉ちゃんです
Double
Oh, is that a new costume?
お　今日は新しい衣裳だね
We asked to have our costumes match these scarves!
このマフラーに合わせてコーディネートしてもらったんです
おお　　じゃ　　もしかして
Are those presents from someone important?
大事な人からのプレゼント
A precious friend of ours knitted them for us.
大切な友達が編んでくれたんです
It made us super happy!
私達すっごく嬉しくて
Right?
ねー
Here's the full payment.
残りの代金は
痺れるね
How electrifying.
Are you satisfied now?
これでいいだろ
Hurry and cure Himari.
速くひまりを治せ
あー　つまらないな
You're no fun.
先生
Doctor!
ひまり　どうした
Himari... what is it?
先生　あのマフラー　ダブルエイチが
Doctor, those scarves... Double-H...!
They're wearing those scarves on TV!
だから　今テレビで二人があのマフラーを
どうして
How?
Was it you?
先生が
That was electrifying, Dr. Sanetoshi!
痺れました　　眞悧先生
It's no big deal.
まあまあ　大げさだよ
He's amazing.
冠ちゃん　凄いの
I didn't tell him anything, but the doctor sent the scarves to Hibari and Hikari for me!
先生　　私が何も言ってないのに
雲雀ちゃんと光莉ちゃんにマフラー届けてくれたんだよ
先生ありがとう
Thank you, Doctor!
参ったな
Sheesh, you've already found out?
もうバレちゃったか
僕のした事が気に障ったかな
Are you upset about what I've done?
No, I appreciate it.
いいえ　礼を言います
But how did you know about the idols?
でも　何故あのアイドルの事を
It's a doctor's job to know everything about his patients.
患者の全てを知るのが医者の務めだからね
妹さんに愛されているか　そんなに不安
Are you really that insecure about whether your sister loves you?
What?
ね　家族と言うのは一種の幻想
Don't you think families are a sort of fantasy,
呪いのような物だと思わない
a curse of sorts?
考えてもみなよ
Think about it.
家族と言う名に縛られて苦しむ子供がどれだけいるか
Just how many children suffer because they're bound to their family?
Parents who treat their children as objects in the name of love, abusing them.
愛と言う名目で子供を私物化する親
殴る親
彼らが愛しているのは自分自身だけだというのに
They only love themselves,
子供はただ家族と言う理由で親を愛し　兄弟を愛さなければならない
yet kids must love their parents solely because they're family,
and love their siblings.
Today's
Slogan
What are you trying to say?
何が言いたい
I wonder.
さあ
I thought that was what was on your mind.
僕はてっきり君がそう思っているんじゃないかと
だって　君は
I mean, wouldn't it be easier on you if they weren't your family?
彼らと家族でいない方が楽なんだろう
What are you talking about?
何を言ってる
The thought never even crossed my mind.
考えた事もない
Really?
そう　ならいいんだ
That's good to hear.
Don't Play
with Straps
Momoka. I guess it has to be you.
桃果　やっぱり私は貴方じゃなきゃだめ
So...
だから
Gosh, I must crush it soon.
嫌だわ　速くすり潰さないと
Are you finished with your meal?
お食事はお済ですね
I'll clear it away then.
お下げします
Sorry, but could you hurry?
悪いけど　速くして
はい
Certainly.
そういえば　お客様
By the way, have you seen her yet?
お逢いになりました
I hear a famous actress is staying here tonight.
今日は有名な女優さんがお泊りになっているんですって
Oh?
そう
It's all the buzz among the housekeepers.
仲居達の間ではその噂でもう持ち切り
Even the cooks were talking about getting an autograph to display in the lobby.
板さんまでサインをいただいてロビーにかざろうなんて
But...
でも　私はどうにも芸能人って言う人達を好きになれません
I somehow can't bring myself to love celebrities.
Oh? Why?
あら　何故
They're always desperate for love.
ああいう人たちはいつも愛に飢えてるんですよ
They were never told they were wanted when they were little.
幼い頃に貴方は必要だって言われたことがないんです
That's why they're consumed by the desire to make up for their childhood.
だから大人になって自分の生い立ちに復讐しようと　躍起になる
"It has to be you."
貴方じゃなくっちゃだめなの
そんな言葉をいつも求めている
They're always seeking such words.
What are you trying to say, Housekeeper?
何が言いたいの　　仲居さん
I'm taking the other half of the diary!
日記の半分　私がいただこう
Not bad.
やるわね
Don't underestimate actresses.
女優を甘く見ないことね
分かったわよ
So, you have the other half of the diary.
残り半分の日記は貴方が持っているのね
だったら　何
What if I did?
It won't be only half for much longer.
もうすぐ半分じゃなくなる
That's all there is to it.
それだけの事よ
Looks like neither of us are willing to back down.
お互い譲る気はなさそうね
エスメラルダ
Esmeralda!
No matter how much they pamper you,
貴方はどんなにちやほやされていようと
you'll always be waking up from a nightmare all alone!
毎朝誰もいなくなった悪夢が目を覚ますのも
A pitiful woman who has to be constantly wanted by someone to be at ease.
常に誰かに必要とされていないと　不安で仕方がない可哀相な人
You talk as if you've seen it all.
まるで見てきたようなお話をするのね
Yes, I've researched you quite thoroughly.
ええ
貴方の事は随分　調べさせてもらいましたから
Oh, no!
しまった
Got it!
ゲット
It's cold!
寒い
Oginome?
荻野目さん
Nothing happened, right?
何も　なかったよな
Oh? Why don't you take advantage of her?
あら　襲っちゃえばいいのに
Yuri...
百合さん
Someone came to steal the diary while you were passed out here.
貴方がここで伸びている間に　日記を奪いに来た人間がいたわよ
ええ
Don't worry.
安心しなさい
ネズミはダミーを掴まされて　海へ逃げたわ
The rat took the bait and escaped into the sea.
You have to leave your valuables in the safe!
貴重品は金庫に入れておかなくちゃね
That's...
それは
Yes. I was the one who stole half of it from Ringo.
そう　リンゴちゃんから半分奪ったのは私
I absolutely must have this diary.
私にはどうしてもこの日記が必要なの
Yuri - The Room Where  That Tower Can be Seen - The Ugly Duckling Play -- Final Act - I saw her love through the window! It was a fated encounter. I was forgiven for my sins.
Daddy?
パパ
あー　違う
It's different!
Daddy's tower changed!
パパのタワーが違う
Savior of the World
届かない思い
The scenery really has changed!
ホントに風景が変わってしまった
引き裂かれてく絆
Was it really because of Momoka's spell?
まさかホントに桃果の呪文で
The girl suddenly burst into flames!
女の子が　急に燃えたんだってさ
何もなかったように
How?
どうして
No idea.
さあ
雲が流れてくいさ
Momoka!
桃果
灰色の水曜日よ
パパは返ってこないわ
Daddy isn't coming back.
He won't ever again.
もう帰ってこないよ
He was left behind with that tower.
前のタワーと一緒に行ってしまったから
さあ　思い出して
You used your spell?
呪文を使ったのね
輝いていた頃を
Yes.
うん
This is the price for setting me free, then?
じゃこれは私を自由にした代償なのね
何もかもまぶしくて
Why did you do something like that?
どうしてそんなことを
恋に落ちてた頃を
だめ
No!
乗り換えに近づいてはだめ
You can't come near the transfers.
さあ　思い出して
You'll lose things important to you as payment.
代償として大切な物を失う事になるわ
Then, why did you...
なら　どうして　桃果は
愛し合ってた頃を
だって　　私は百合の事が大好きだから
Because I love you a lot, Yuri.
真剣な眼差しで
見つめ合ってた頃を
You're beautiful the way you are now.
百合は今のままでとても綺麗だよ
さあ　思い出して
Momoka disappeared after that incident.
その後　桃果はあの事件で姿を消した
輝いていた頃を
桃果は乗り換えをしたんだ
Momoka had taken another transfer.
夢に生きてた頃を
The scenery of the world changed.
世界の風景は変わった
愛し合ってた頃を
This time, I'll use the diary's spells to transfer to another fate.
今度は私が日記の呪文で運命を乗り換える
I will bring Momoka back to this world.
桃果をこちらの世界に取り戻すのだ
That man dominates everything in this world, the present.
私達は今も全てをあの男に支配されている
So, I have decided to crush him.
だから私は彼をすり潰すことにした
Lily Hoshino
生存戦略　　フィレンツェから届きました